{
    "id": "633a027adab745388bd9be20638e88e6",
    "title": "For, Since, In and From",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I once studied classical music ……………… six months.",
            "description": "We use 'for' with a period of time. ",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c150a7eb9bff46fb9dc5c4049417b10a"
        },
        {
            "question": "That house has been empty …………….. six months.",
            "description": "Use 'for' with a period of time.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "162ea11523e84fc1a4c92aa56a3a2ab2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to France ……………… the summer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "47dbb6a253fc43109aeb5c50fcf33405"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have known him ………………. our school days.",
            "description": "We use since with the starting point of actions or situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "341826e9647c413c84af088d6dd6b593"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have known him ……………… a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6277cdde7e24da889d0a8092a329ade"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long have you been here ………………?",
            "description": "We use for to indicate duration.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c0fd6323da7f48e08cc36ab4987fa7db"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t met him ………………… months.",
            "description": "After negatives and superlatives, 'in' can be used to talk about duration.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "for",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c56aac8cd5e943a5a96bab8fde3fe9b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was the worst storm ………………… decades.",
            "description": "After negatives and superlatives, 'in' can be used to talk about duration.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "for",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "79cdb090cd41423fb885349f616acecd"
        },
        {
            "question": "He loved music ……………….. his earliest childhood.",
            "description": "'From' can be used with a present perfect tense in expressions that mean 'right from the start'.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "from",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6c15c53a617f4e33ab15814119d8c650"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be at home ........................... morning on.",
            "description": "Both since and from can be used to give the starting point of actions. Since is mainly used with perfect tenses. From is used in other cases.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b7ace9366f5e47b5895187a53b0076a4"
        }
    ]
}